Piotr Murias

Poland



piotr.murias@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/muriasp

Summary

Experienced in:

Process Creation and Improvement, Program and Project Management, Service Management, Platform as a Service, Computerized Systems Validation (including Cloud Validation) - Dreamforce speaker, IT Governance, IT Security and Risk Management, Software Development Life Cycle, Agile/Scrum/ITIL experienced, People/Team Management, Salesforce.com Platform Management, Movie Production, Video Editing

Experience

Be Manager

Be | Shaping the Future Poland

Mar 2019 - Present (4 years 2 months)

Head of Innovation & Cloud Technologies

- Project management including mobilization (e.g. team staffing, planning), execution and coordination
- · Driving entire project life-cycle from initiation to closure
- Monitoring project financials, scope, and schedule
- Acting as primary day-to-day point of contact for the clients
- Providing leadership for operational aspects of the project
- Facilitating regular status meetings with project team, sponsors, and all stakeholders
- Generating and distributing status reports, time usage reports and expense reports
- Assessing and managing project risks
- Preparing/supporting delivery of client presentations during sales cycle, requirements, design, pilot and user

acceptance testing sessions

- Reviewing deliverables prepared by the team
- · Providing mentoring, guidance and coaching to project team members
- Providing pre-sales support

Business Development Manager

Cambria Systems

Nov 2015 - Feb 2018 (2 years 4 months)

Identifying and searching for market needs to create new products.

Working with sales and marketing teams in order to prepare the product for release.

Working with technical leaders team to catch new trends and innovations.

Building new products and moving them to sales team.

Focusing on growing and developing existing clients, together with generating new business.

Identify new sales opportunities within existing and new accounts

Creating and improving sales process with CRM implementation.



Team Lead (Senior Solution Specialist)

Roche

May 2012 - Oct 2015 (3 years 6 months)

Managing Salesforce.com Administrators (SFDC deployers, Heroku, ETL, Oracle).

Team administration focusing on innovations and delivering service for projects and applications on Salesforce.com platform.

Responsible for new recruitment, budget, training.

Validation of Salesforce.com platform (DF14 speaker) introducing new solution of cloud validation.

Optimizing processes for better platform efficiency and security (Access Management, Environment Strategy, SSO, Continuous Integration, Monitoring).

Governance for CRM and non-CRM applications/projects on Salesforce platform.

Creating release management and standard operation procedures for SFDC related applications/ projects and support teams. Project manager for Salesforce.com platform enhancements and applications.

Member of Salesforce.com Governance Board at Roche.

Working in a global team.

Responsible for organizations with over 20 000 business users and 25 million characters of Apex Code in production

Application Manager (Senior Solution Specialist)

Roche

2010 - 2012 (2 years)

Responsible for sample logistics at Roche.

Responsibility for operating procedures.

Coordinating samples databases in 3 global locations and collaboration with business partners.

Security Administrator (Solution Specialist, Senior Solution Specialist)

Roche

May 2005 - Dec 2009 (4 years 8 months)

Security Administrator for Oracle Clinical (medical database collected and processed during the drug lifecycle) and additional supporting tools.

Responsible security procedures and processes followed by Security Team globally.

Involved in the process of creation Shared Services Center at Roche

Change Management Coordinator (Senior Solution Specialist)

Roche

2008 - 2009 (1 year)

Responsible for change management and problem management processes. Supporting Oracle Clinical and surrounding applications according to CSV and regulatory regulations.

Maintenance of Oracle Clinical Portal used globally by internal/external clinical, lab managers and monitors.

System Administrator

Airpolonia Sp Z o.o Jun 2004 - Dec 2004 (7 months) RADIXX system administration. Responsible for creating procedures.

Creating/modifying flights schedules.

Training employees on airports (Poland and abroad).

Contact with airline companies and airports.

Implementing changes and upgrades in system.

Education



Polish-Japanese Academy of Information Technology

Bachelor of Science, Animation, Interactive Technology, Video Graphics and Special **Effects**

1999 - 2003

Licenses & Certifications



ITIL v3 Foundation - EXIN

00031571

Skills

Salesforce.com • Cross-functional Team Leadership • Software Project Management • Scrum • Software Development • ITIL • PaaS • Video Editing • After Effects • Film Production